Too big to fail.
Megalodon Rising is a action, science fiction film directed by Brian Nowak.
When history’s greatest aquatic predator returns, the armada of
modern warships sent to destroy it has no chance at all.
Moore, played by Tom Sizemore.
Lt. Commander Ahearn, played by O'Shay Neal.
Captain Lynch, played by Wynter Eddins.
Dr. Lee, played by Freda Yifan Jing.
Captain Ping, played by Zhan Wang.
First Mate Tan, played by Adam He.
The Asylum is an American independent film company and distributor that
focuses on producing low-budget, direct-to-video films.
The company has produced titles that capitalize on productions by major studios, often using film titles
and scripts very similar to those of current blockbusters in order to lure customers.
These titles have been dubbed "mockbusters" by the press.
The film explores themes of shark attack, shark, megalodon.
The tone is thought_provoking.